[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is best describes the cause of Parkinsons disease?", "correct_answer": "A decrease in a neurotransmitter", "incorrect_answers": ["A brain injury", "Changes in the myelin sheath of the neuron", "Decreased blood flow to the brain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country is the leader in beer consumption (per capita).", "correct_answer": "Czech Republic", "incorrect_answers": ["USA", "Austria", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term thrombo, which comes from Greek, refers to a blood clot.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This popular cocktail, usually garnished with a cherry, contains rye or bourbon whiskey mixed with sweet vermouth.", "correct_answer": "Manhattan", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba Libre", "Cosmopolitan", "Margarita"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor played partner/ sidekick and fellow escaped convict to John Goodmans character, in the 1987 Coen brothers movie Raising Arizona.", "correct_answer": "William Forsythe", "incorrect_answers": ["William H. Macy", "John Turturro", "Nicholas Cage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the two products that Uncle Rico tries to sell door-to-door?", "correct_answer": "Tupperware and bust enhancer", "incorrect_answers": ["footballs and weight-loss pills", "Bibles and maps", "steaks and miniature ship replicas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Basketball has always been a physical sport. This player is a record breaker for the most personal fouls in one NBA season.", "correct_answer": "Darryl Dawkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Moses Malone", "Joe Dumars", "Wilt  Chamberlin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Dorothys surname in the 1939 classic The Wizard of Oz?", "correct_answer": "Gale", "incorrect_answers": ["Hill", "Dale", "Baxter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Native American folklore told of calm spirits who lived inside each kernel of popcorn, but they got angry if their homes were heated and finally burst out. In reality, what do these spirits represent?", "correct_answer": "Water and starch", "incorrect_answers": ["Starch and air", "Air and water", "Air and corn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The guinea pig is unable to produce this substance in its own body and gets it from its food.", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Saliva", "Stomach acid", "Digestive enzymes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ruler of the Mughal Empire Akbar the Great was very enamored with cheetahs and it is said he kept a stable of how many of these cats?", "correct_answer": "1,000", "incorrect_answers": ["5,000", "750", "500"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Malone, Burt Reynolds character had previously worked for this organization before going to the Pacific Northwest with his ailing Ford Mustang.", "correct_answer": "C.I.A.", "incorrect_answers": ["Secret Service", "F.B.I.", "Green Beret"]}]